<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CV on Emil Bakkensen Johansen</title>
    <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CV on Emil Bakkensen Johansen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MSc in Sociology, University of Copenhagen</title>
      <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/msc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/msc/</guid>
      <description>Specialization in Knowledge, Organization and Politics.
GPA: 11.3.
Grade 12 (A) for final master&amp;rsquo;s thesis: &amp;ldquo;Non-human actants on the frontlines of #Hongkong. A digital sociological paper about the Anti-ELAB movement and its symbol construction on Twitter.&amp;quot;
 Scraping of 1.6 million tweets about the protests Dictionary classification (machine learning) Object detection in 700,000 images (YOLOv4) Network analysis (Gephi) Actor-network theory Python coding  Selection of courses completed:
 Digital Methods: From Facebook Ethnography to Computational Social Science Governed by Algorithms - Facebook, Google, and the re-programming of digital citizens Democratic Innovations and Civic Participation Problematization Analysis: How and Why something is and became a Social Problem  Here is my master&amp;rsquo;s degree certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIVE - The Danish Center for Social Science Research</title>
      <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/vive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/vive/</guid>
      <description>I was employed at VIVE from August 2019 to June 2021 as a Student Assistant.
My tasks as student assistant was to assist on multiple projects within different welfare sectors. I collected qualitative/ quantitative data, coded in STATA, screened literature and co-authored reports.
The scope of the projects I worked on ranged from (but was not limited to):
 Children homicide committed by parents Relatives to people experiencing domestic violence Assessment of citizens with a combination of mental health sickness and substance abuse  Read report about the subject that I co-authored here (in Danish)   Voluntary support interventions for at-risk families  Read report about the subject that I co-authored here (in Danish)   Sugardating among Danish youth Family law  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BSc in Sociology, University of Copenhagen</title>
      <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/bsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/bsc/</guid>
      <description>GPA: 9.0
Grade 10 (B) for my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis: &amp;ldquo;You wouldn&amp;rsquo;t steal a car: a sociological study of online piracy&amp;rdquo;
 Qualitative interviews with online pirates Symbolic interactionism Neutralization techniques Consumption and identity  Selection of courses completed:
 Political Sociology Advanced Quantitative Methods Advanced Qualitative Methods Race/Gender/Surveillance Globalization and Social Media  Here is my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exchange at The University of Texas at Austin</title>
      <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/uta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/uta/</guid>
      <description>I spent the Fall semester of 2017 as an exchange student in Austin, Texas. Here, I studied media, intersectionality and surveillance, while improving my English proficiencies.
Courses completed:
 Race/Gender/Surveillance Globalization and Social Media Sociological Theory Sociology of Criminal Justice  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The National Board of Social Services (Socialstyrelsen)</title>
      <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/socialstyrelsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/socialstyrelsen/</guid>
      <description>At The National Board of Social Services I was employed from February 2018 to July 2019 as a Student Assistant.
I was part of a team that focused on youth at risk and assisted with planning events for service practitioners, set up surveys and gained experience with the Danish state apparatus. Furthermore, I updated the webpages for different projects and assisted in case management for Danish government funds (Satspuljen).
Here is a selection of projects I assisted on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danske Bank</title>
      <link>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/danskebank/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilbakke.github.io/website/post/danskebank/</guid>
      <description>I was employed at Danske Bank as an IT Supporter from March 2015 to June 2015.
From Danske Bank headquarters I was an IT Supporter for the bank&amp;rsquo;s MobilePay service, assisting customers with difficulties via phone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
